Scenic Hudson, Inc. Administrative History Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- Printed Material, 1964-2000; 5; 8.67 linear foot Boxes: 20 - 46 Folders: 174 - 544
  - Scenic Hudson Inc. Publications and Reports, 1965-2000; 5.6
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin #15, 05/17/1966 (Folder 321, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin #16, 05/01/1966 (Folder 322, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin #17, 06/27/1966 (Folder 323, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin #18, 08/15/1966 (Folder 324, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin #19, 09/20/1966 (Folder 325, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin #20, 01/04/1967 (Folder 326, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin #21, 01/13/1967 (Folder 327, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin #22, 03/28/1967 (Folder 328, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin #23, 06/13/1967 (Folder 329, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Special Bulletin, 1968 (Folder 330, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Special Bulletin, 10/2/1968 (Folder 331, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin #27, 10/1968 (Folder 332, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin #28, 01/1969 (Folder 333, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin #29, 02/11/1969 (Folder 334, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin #30, 04/1969 (Folder 335, Box 31)
    - Assessing the Impact of Development on Scenic Resource of the Hudson River (Folder 336, Box 32)
    - Understanding Traffic (Folder 337, Box 32)
    - Forgetting PCB Dumpsites of the Upper Hudson Valley (Folder 338, Box 32)
    - Advances in Dredging (Folder 339, Box 32)
    - The Real Cost of Development (Folder 340, Box 32)
    - Signs of the Times (Folder 341, Box 32)
    - Dealing with Airport Growth (Folder 342, Box 32)
    - Integrating Public Access with Private Development (Folder 343, Box 32)
    - WE, West meets East, June 1991 (Folder 344, Box 32)
    - Bill Roth Graphics (Folder 345, Box 33)
    - Original Layouts, Long Range Plan, December 1988 (Folder 346, Box 33)
    - Storm King Propaganda (Folder 347, Box 33)
    - Challenge on the Hudson Propaganda (Folder 348, Box 33)
    - Samples of Scenic Hudson Stationary (Folder 349, Box 33)
  - Reports, 1975-1979; 5.7
    Water Studies; Scenic Hudson Inc. Publications and Reports,
    - Hudson River Basin, Water and Related Lan Resources Study, Technical Paper 1 (Folder 350, Box 34)
    - Hudson River Basin, Water and Related Lan Resources Study, Technical Paper 2 (Folder 351, Box 34)
    - Hudson River Basin, Water and Related Lan Resources Study, Technical Paper 4 (Folder 352, Box 34)
    - Hudson River Basin, Water and Related Lan Resources Study, Technical Paper 5 (Folder 353, Box 34)
    - Influence of the Proposed Cornwall Pumps Storage Project and Steam Electric Generating Plants on the Hudson River Estuary with Emphasis on Striped Bass and Other Fish Populations, July 1978 (Folder 354, Box 34)
    - 1976 Year Class Report for the Multiplant Impact Study of the Hudson River Estuary, May 1979 (Folder 355, Box 35)
    - Hudson River Ecological Study on the Area of Indian Point, 1978 Annual Report (Folder 356, Box 35)
    - New York State Coastal Management Program, March 1979 (Folder 357, Box 35)
    - The New York Power System Generation and Transmission Plans, 1971-1980 (Folder 358, Box 35)
    - Hudson Highlands Preservation Study (Folder 359, Box 36)
    - Larval Exclusion Systems for Power Plant Cooling Water Intakes, February 1978 (Folder 360, Box 36)
    - New York State Energy Conference Proceedings, September 20, 21, 1978 (Folder 361, Box 36)
    - Establishing and Energy Policy for New York State, 1975 (Folder 362, Box 36)
    - The Price of Power, Electric Utilities and the Environment (Folder 363, Box 36)
    - Thermal Effects Literature Review for Hudson River Representative Important Species, March 1978 (Folder 364, Box 36)
    - Effects of Heat Shock on Predation of Striped bass larvae by Yearling White Perch (Folder 365, Box 36)
    - The 1978 Annual Report of The Standing Committee on Environmental Conservation (Folder 366, Box 36)
    - Hudson River Basin Plan, A Water quality Management Plan (Folder 367, Box 36)
    - Tappan Zee Corridor Study, Phase III Report (Folder 368, Box 36)
    - URS, Technical Memorandum no. 1 (Folder 369, Box 36)
    - URS, Technical Memorandum No. 2 (Folder 370, Box 36)
    - URS, Technical Memorandum No. 3 (Folder 371, Box 36)
    - Indian Point Generating Station a 316(a) Demonstration (Folder 372, Box 37)
    - Indian Point Generating Station a 316(a) Demonstration, Appendix D (Folder 373, Box 37)
    - Indian Point Generating Station Entrainment and Near Field River Studies, 1978 Annual Report (Folder 374, Box 37)
    - Hudson River Ecological Study in the Area of Indian Point, 1977 Annual Report (Folder 375, Box 37)
    - Impingement: An Annotated Bibliography EPRI EA-1050 (Folder 376, Box 38)
    - Entrainment: An Annotated Bibliography EPRI EA-1049 (Folder 377, Box 38)
    - Ecosystem Effects of Phytoplankton and Zooplankton Entrainment EPRI EA-1038 (Folder 378, Box 38)
    - Synthesis and Analysis of Ecological Information From Cooling Impounds, Volume 1 EPRI EA-1054 (Folder 379, Box 38)
    - Synthesis and Analysis of Ecological Information From Cooling Impoundments Volume 2: Appendix A- Study Site Histories and Data Synopsis EPRI EA-1054 (Folder 380, Box 38)
    - Proceedings: Advisory Workshop to Identify Research Needs on the Formation Of Acid Precipitation EPRI EA-1074 (Folder 381, Box 38)
    - Chemical effects of Power Plant Cooling Water: An Annotated Bibliography EPRI EA-1072 (Folder 382, Box 38)
    - Biofouling Control Investigations:18- Month Summary Report EPRI EA-1082 (Folder 383, Box 38)
  - Pamphlets and Brochures, 1963-2001; 5.8
    Guides to various places in the Hudson River Valley, and Dutchess County and its surrounding areas
    - Heritage Trials, New York (Folder 384, Box 39)
    - Hudson River Valley Travel Guide (Folder 385, Box 39)
    - Land and People, Annual Report, 1996 (Folder 386, Box 39)
    - Marist College Report of Gifts, 1998 (Folder 387, Box 39)
    - Open Space Institute, 20th Anniversary Report (Folder 388, Box 39)
    - NYS Bridge Authority, Annual Report, 1996 (Folder 389, Box 39)
    - NYSERDA, Annual Report, 1997-98 (Folder 390, Box 39)
    - Delaware River Basin Commission, Annual Report, 1996 (Folder 391, Box 39)
    - Vistas and Vision- A History of the NY/NJ Trail Conference (Folder 392, Box 39)
    - Green County Travel Guide (Folder 393, Box 39)
    - Hudson River Maritime Museum, 1999, “The Pilot’s Log” (Folder 394, Box 39)
    - A Catalogue of Material Relating to the History of New York, Fall 2000 (Folder 395, Box 39)
    - West Point Guide Book (Folder 396, Box 39)
    - Hudson Valley Guide, Summer 2000 (Folder 397, Box 39)
    - Poets Walk (Folder 398, Box 39)
    - Highland Flings Escape Manual (Folder 399, Box 39)
    - The Hudson River Valley Is Really Going Places (Japanese) (Folder 400, Box 39)
    - The Hudson River Valley is Really Going Places (Folder 401, Box 39)
    - Wilderstein (Folder 402, Box 40)
    - unnyside (Folder 403, Box 40)
    - Union Church of Pocantico Hills (Folder 404, Box 40)
    - Dutchess County Farm Produce Map (Folder 405, Box 40)
    - Explore Historic Hudson Valley (Folder 406, Box 40)
    - Hudson Basin River Watch (Folder 407, Box 40)
    - Exploring New York’s Past (Folder 408, Box 40)
    - Visitor’s Guide to Marist College and The Historic Hudson Valley (Folder 409, Box 40)
    - Hudson River Heritage (Folder 410, Box 40)
    - Welcome to the Culinary Institute of America (Folder 411, Box 40)
    - National Trusts Historic Sites Handbook (Folder 412, Box 40)
    - Restaurant and Lodging Guide, Cold Spring and Garrison (Folder 413, Box 40)
    - Bykenhulle House (Folder 414, Box 40)
    - N.Y.S. Corps Collaboration (Folder 415, Box 40)
    - Beekman Arms (Folder 416, Box 40)
    - Kingston (Folder 417, Box 40)
    - Passport to the Historic Landmarks of the Hudson Valley (Folder 418, Box 40)
    - Frances Lehmon Corporate Art Center (Folder 419, Box 40)
    - Montgomery Place (Folder 420, Box 40)
    - Mills Mansion (Folder 421, Box 40)
    - Home of F.D.R (Folder 422, Box 40)
    - CIA Four Fine Restaurants (Folder 423, Box 40)
    - Visitors Guide Shaupeneak Ridge (Folder 424, Box 40)
    - Historic River Towns of Westchester (Folder 425, Box 40)
    - Riverbank State Park (Folder 426, Box 40)
    - N.Y.S. Parks, Historical Sites, and Programs Guide (Folder 427, Box 40)
    - historic Ossining (Folder 428, Box 40)
    - Hudson River Quarterly, Winter 1979 (Folder 429, Box 40)
    - Three Views on the power Crisis (Folder 430, Box 40)
    - Hawk Mountain Sanctuary (Folder 431, Box 40)
    - Orange County Visitors Guide (Folder 432, Box 40)
    - Recycle (Folder 433, Box 40)
    - Mile by Mile, Storm King Mountain (Folder 434, Box 40)
    - “It’s a Victory” (Folder 435, Box 40)
    - Will Our Children Inherit This Hudson River? (Folder 436, Box 40)
    - Discover Rivers Park (Folder 437, Box 40)
    - The Saugerties Lighthouse Conservancy (Folder 438, Box 40)
    - Storm King Art Center (Folder 439, Box 40)
    - Hudson River Conservation Land Trust (Folder 440, Box 40)
    - Train Map of: Rams Horn-Livingston Sanctuary (Folder 441, Box 40)
    - The Fishkill United Methodist Church (Folder 442, Box 40)
    - “We were There When” (Folder 443, Box 40)
    - Save Storm King Mountain (Folder 444, Box 40)
    - Planned Giving (Folder 445, Box 40)
    - Scenic Hudson Quarter of a Century Achievements (Folder 446, Box 40)
    - The Significance and Future use of the Storm King Papers (Folder 447, Box 40)
    - What is Scenic Hudson (Folder 448, Box 40)
    - It’s a ? of Environment (Folder 449, Box 40)
    - A friend of the River (Folder 450, Box 40)
    - Scenic Hudson Deserves Your Support (Folder 451, Box 40)
    - Environmental Litigation Clinic (Folder 452, Box 40)
    - Earthcare (Folder 453, Box 40)
    - Annual N.S. Environmental Congress, 10/27/73 (Folder 454, Box 40)
    - Keep America Beautiful (Folder 455, Box 40)
    - Wetlands Conference, 10/9/74 (Folder 456, Box 40)
    - Cape May: Places to Eat, Shop and Stay (Folder 457, Box 41)
    - Hudson River Valley Recreation Map (Folder 458, Box 41)
    - Calender of the Season at Boscobel (Folder 459, Box 41)
    - DEC Pamphlet: Saving our Senic Roads (Folder 460, Box 41)
    - Guide Map to Historic Kingston (Folder 461, Box 41)
    - Clermont State Historic Site (Folder 462, Box 41)
    - Washington’s Headquarters (Folder 463, Box 41)
    - Piermont on Hudson (Folder 464, Box 41)
    - An Invitation to Kykuit (Folder 465, Box 41)
    - The Hudson River Travel Guide (Folder 466, Box 41)
    - Kaatsban International Dance Center, Inc. (Folder 467, Box 41)
    - Celtic Day in the Park, 9/29/69 (Folder 468, Box 41)
    - First Hudson Valley Wine and Food Festival (Folder 469, Box 41)
    - Ninth Annual Huson Valley Country Setas Tours (Folder 470, Box 41)
    - Locust Grove: A National Historic Landmark (Folder 471, Box 41)
    - Hudson River Waterfront Map 2000 (Folder 472, Box 41)
    - Hudson River Waterfront Map 2001 (Folder 473, Box 41)
    - About Scenic Roads (Folder 474, Box 41)
    - Historic Hudson Valley (Folder 475, Box 41)
    - Appalachian Mountain Club, Jan.-April Winter Schedule 1998 (Folder 476, Box 41)
    - Mohonk Mountain House (Folder 477, Box 41)
    - The Hyde Park Train (Folder 478, Box 41)
    - Mohonk Preserve- Trapp’s Gateway Interpretive Center (Folder 479, Box 41)
    - Hudson River Valley Reginal Travel Guide (Folder 480, Box 41)
    - Gomez Mill House (Folder 481, Box 41)
    - Popular cience: How safe are our dams? (Folder 482, Box 41)
    - NYS Parks and Historic Sites Guide (Folder 483, Box 41)
    - NYS Parks Golf Guide (Folder 484, Box 41)
    - Reader’s Digest, February 1969 (Folder 485, Box 41)
    - Boscobel (Folder 486, Box 41)
    - The Hudson in Story and Pictures, 1770-1870 (Folder 487, Box 41)
    - Environmental Law Pamphlet for Symposium, 10/18/75 (Folder 489, Box 41)
    - American Heritage Society (Folder 490, Box 41)
    - Blenheium-Gilboa: Pumped Storage Power Plant (Folder 491, Box 41)
  - Magazines, 1964-1999; 5.9
    Magazines, A-Z
    - Audobon, July/August 1968 (Folder 492, Box 42)
    - Between the Lines (Folder 493, Box 42)
    - Brooklyn Union Gas (Folder 494, Box 42)
    - Building the American Commons (Folder 495, Box 42)
    - The Conservationist (Folder 496, Box 42)
    - Environmental (Folder 497, Box 42)
    - EPA Journal (Folder 498, Box 42)
    - The First Decade and Beyond (Folder 499, Box 42)
    - Forbes, September 1, 1964 (Folder 500, Box 42)
    - Gas (Folder 501, Box 42)
    - The General Electric Forum (Folder 502, Box 42)
    - Homebuyers Guide (Folder 503, Box 42)
    - Hudson Valley Magazine, 1995 - 1996 (Folder 504, Box 42)
    - Hudson Valley Magazine, September 1991 (Folder 505, Box 42)
    - Hudson Valley Region, Rockland County (Folder 506, Box 42)
    - Institute of Ecosystems Studies (Folder 507, Box 43)
    - Land and People (Folder 508, Box 43)
    - Land Trust Review (Folder 509, Box 43)
    - The Living Wilderness (Folder 510, Box 43)
    - Marist College Report (Folder 511, Box 43)
    - Natural Resource Defense Council (Folder 512, Box 43)
    - New Jersey Conservation (Folder 513, Box 43)
    - New York (Folder 514, Box 43)
    - Open Space (Folder 515, Box 43)
    - Power, 1965 (Folder 516, Box 43)
    - Power, 1966 (Folder 517, Box 43)
    - Protecting the Source (Folder 518, Box 43)
    - Rails to Trail, winter 1999 (Folder 519, Box 44)
    - Scenic Hudson’s Challenge of the Hudson, 1999 (Folder 520, Box 44)
    - Scientific America (Folder 521, Box 44)
    - Shaping the Future (Folder 522, Box 44)
    - Sierra Club (Folder 523, Box 44)
    - Smithsonian (Folder 524, Box 44)
    - Stewardship (Folder 525, Box 44)
    - Time (Folder 526, Box 44)
  - Misc. Printed Material, 1965-1979; 5.10
    Other various printed materials that could not be categorized
    - The Issue at Storm King Mountain, 1965 (Folder 527, Box 45)
    - Cornwall Hydroelectric Project (Folder 528, Box 45)
    - The Hudson (Folder 529, Box 45)
    - The Cornwall Project (Folder 530, Box 45)
    - Answer to the Electirc World Ad in the New York Times, Ocotober 6, 1969 (Folder 531, Box 45)
    - Scenic Hudson Prevention Conference, 1967-1970s (Folder 532, Box 45)
    - “An Alternative to Storm King”, 1973 (Folder 533, Box 45)
    - ICONN Erie Project, 1980 (Folder 534, Box 45)
    - Miscellaneous (Folder 535, Box 45)
    - Misc. Brochures (Folder 536, Box 45)
    - Central Hudson Gas and Electric Corp. Annual Reports, 1978-1979 (Folder 537, Box 45)
    - That River’s Alive- The Majestic Hudson Makes a Comeback (Folder 538, Box 45)
    - The New York Botanical Garden Spring Tour 1970 (Folder 539, Box 46)
    - Mailings (Folder 540, Box 46)
    - Misc. Scenic Hudson Pamphlets (Folder 541, Box 46)
    - Misc. Recycling Information (Folder 542, Box 46)
    - Storm King Pamphlets (Folder 543, Box 46)
    - Misc. Guides (Folder 544, Box 46)
- Events, 1966-1976; 6; 1.33 linear feet Boxes: 47 - 50 Folders: 545 - 605
  Events hosted and/or sponsored by Scenic Hudson, Inc.
  - Harvard Club Cocktail Party 11/10/1966 (Folder 545, Box 47)
  - Harvard Club Luncheon 03/11/1966 (Folder 546, Box 47)
  - Princeton Club Luncheon 05/26/1966 (Folder 547, Box 47)
  - Boat Ride 11/18/1967 (Folder 548, Box 47)
  - 1967 Boat Ride Literature (Folder 549, Box 47)
  - 1967 Boat Ride Stationary (Folder 550, Box 47)
  - Fund Raising-Princeton Club 03/01/1967 (Folder 551, Box 47)
  - Meeting at Tarrytown House 09/07/1967 (Folder 552, Box 47)
  - Harvard Club Luncheon 04/25/1967 (Folder 553, Box 47)
  - 1967 Conference 11/10/1967 (Folder 554, Box 47)
  - Rothschild Cocktail Party 06/26/1968 (Folder 555, Box 47)
  - Dinner to Honor L.O. Rothschild 1968 (Folder 556, Box 47)
  - 1969 Citizens Conservation Conference 05/20/1969 (Folder 557, Box 47)
  - Citizens Conference Material 05/20/1969 (Folder 558, Box 47)
  - A. Hecksher Speech 05/20/1969 (Folder 559, Box 47)
  - May 20, 1969 Event at Tavern on the Green (Folder 560, Box 47)
  - Citizens Conservation Day 05/20/1969 (Folder 561, Box 47)
  - Salute to Storm King 08/26/1969 (Folder 562, Box 47)
  - Dinner-1969 (Folder 563, Box 47)
  - Lunch 12/09/1969 (Folder 564, Box 47)
  - Fund Raising Williams Club 12/09/1969 (Folder 565, Box 47)
  - Citizens Conservation Conference Attendees 05/20/1969 (Folder 566, Box 47)
  - Yacht Club 5/13/70 (Folder 567, Box 48)
  - Expedition to Black Rock Forest 5/2/70 (Folder 568, Box 48)
  - Boat Ride 1970 (Folder 569, Box 48)
  - Cornwall Meeting 1971 (Folder 570, Box 48)
  - Beautiful Ideas 1971 (Folder 571, Box 48)
  - Symposium 1971 (Folder 572, Box 48)
  - Bear Mountain 1971 (Folder 573, Box 48)
  - 1971 Programs (Folder 574, Box 48)
  - Book Party May 1972 (Folder 575, Box 48)
  - Luncheon Names 1969-1972 (Folder 576, Box 48)
  - Harvard Club Cocktail Party 5/23/72 (Folder 577, Box 48)
  - Picnic 10/14/72 (Folder 578, Box 48)
  - Party for Terry Rotola 11/30/72 (Folder 579, Box 48)
  - Energy Discussion, St. Regis Hotel 4/10/73 (Folder 580, Box 48)
  - April 1973 energy discussion Speeches (Folder 581, Box 48)
  - April 1973 Energy Discussion Correspondence (Folder 582, Box 48)
  - Party at St. Regis 4/10/73 (Folder 583, Box 48)
  - Energy Conference 1973 (Folder 584, Box 48)
  - Stillman Meeting Cornwall, 4/73 (Folder 585, Box 48)
  - N.J. Speech 3/29/73 (Folder 586, Box 48)
  - SHPC 10th Anniversary 1973 (Folder 587, Box 48)
  - Cocktail Party 12/73 (Folder 588, Box 48)
  - Speaking Engagements 1973-1974 (Folder 589, Box 48)
  - Solar Dinner and notes 1974-1975 (Folder 590, Box 49)
  - Solar Committee List 11/10/75 (Folder 591, Box 49)
  - Solar Dinner Correspondence 11/10/75 (Folder 592, Box 49)
  - SHPC Op Sail 1976 (Folder 593, Box 49)
  - Dinner Meeting 1976 (Folder 594, Box 49)
  - Slideshow “The Landscape in the Hudson River Valley” 1976 (Folder 595, Box 49)
  - Wind Program 3/1/76 (Folder 596, Box 49)
  - Kit Material Wind 3/71 (Folder 597, Box 49)
  - Wind Dinner 3/1/76 (Folder 598, Box 49)
  - Winder Energy Discussion 3/1/76 (Folder 599, Box 49)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation Boat Cruises (Folder 600, Box 50)
  - NYC Corporate Breakfast correspondence (Folder 601, Box 50)
  - NYC Corporate Breakfast Miscellaneous (Folder 602, Box 50)
  - NYC Corporate Breakfast Press Releases and clippings (Folder 603, Box 50)
  - NYC Corporate Breakfast Invite Lists (Folder 604, Box 50)
  - River Champions Reception (Folder 605, Box 50)
- Maps, 7; 0.33 linear feet Box: 51 Folders: 606 - 609
  Various maps of the Hudson Valley
  - 1778 Hudson Highlands (Folder 606, Box 51)
  - Maps (Folder 607, Box 51)
  - Wetland Maps (Folder 608, Box 51)
  - Zoning Maps (Folder 609, Box 51)
- Subject Files, 8; 3.67 linear feet Boxes: 52 - 63 Folders: 610 - 763
  Topics of environmental importance and concern researched and referenced by Scenic Hudson, Inc.
  Alphabetical by subject
  - American Electric Power, Press Release (Folder 610, Box 52)
  - American Electric Power, Annual Reports 1963-1966 (Folder 611, Box 52)
  - Application for National Landmarks (Folder 612, Box 52)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, Clippings&Press Releases (Folder 613, Box 52)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, Correspondence (Folder 614, Box 52)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, Legal Material (Folder 615, Box 52)
  - The Balmville Tree (Folder 616, Box 52)
  - Bicentennial Commission, Reports (Folder 617, Box 52)
  - Bicentennial Commission, Correspondence (Folder 618, Box 52)
  - The 1977 Blackout, News Clippings (a) (Folder 619, Box 52)
  - The 1977 Blackout, News Clippings (b) (Folder 620, Box 52)
  - The 1977 Blackout, Correspondence (Folder 621, Box 52)
  - The 1977 Blackout, Correspondence (Folder 622, Box 52)
  - The 1977 Blackout, Publications (Folder 623, Box 52)
  - The 1977 Blackout, Press Releases (Folder 624, Box 52)
  - Burke Estate, Hastings on Hudson (Folder 625, Box 52)
  - (Box 52)
  - Cementon Power Plant, Legal Material (Folder 626, Box 53)
  - Cementon Power Plant, Printed Material (Folder 627, Box 53)
  - Cementon Power Plant, Correspondence (Folder 628, Box 53)
  - Center for the Hudson River Valley, Correspondence (Folder 629, Box 53)
  - Center for the Hudson River Valley, Publications (Folder 630, Box 53)
  - Center for the Hudson River Valley, Miscellaneous (Folder 631, Box 53)
  - Con Ed - P.C.H.S., Correspondence&Testimony (Folder 632, Box 53)
  - Con Ed, 1975 Annual Report (Folder 633, Box 53)
  - Con Ed, Pamphlet - Programs to Protect the National Environment (Folder 634, Box 53)
  - Con Ed, Annual Meeting at Stockholders - 1974 (Folder 635, Box 53)
  - Con Ed, Building the Future - Indian Point (Folder 636, Box 53)
  - Clearwater, Committee Meetings (Folder 637, Box 53)
  - Clearwater, Weekly Highlights (Folder 638, Box 53)
  - Clearwater, Correspondence (Folder 639, Box 53)
  - Clearwater, By-Laws (Folder 640, Box 53)
  - Clearwater, Sloop Restoration (Folder 641, Box 53)
  - Clearmont Rodeo&Ranch, Correspondence (Folder 642, Box 53)
  - Fish&Wildlife, Impact Review Team (Folder 643, Box 54)
  - Fish&Wildlife, Misc. Correspondence (Folder 644, Box 54)
  - Fish&Wildlife, Hudson River Technical Committee (Folder 645, Box 54)
  - Fish&Wildlife, Hudson River Policy Committee (Folder 646, Box 54)
  - Fish&Wildlife, Meetings (Folder 647, Box 54)
  - Fish&Wildlife, Correspondence w/ Washington Office (Folder 648, Box 54)
  - Garden Club, Water Exhibit&Speech, 1983 (Folder 649, Box 54)
  - Garden Club, Correspondence for 1982 Exhibit (Folder 650, Box 54)
  - Governor Rockefeller, Correspondence 1966-1970 (Folder 651, Box 54)
  - Governor Rockefeller, Misc. (Folder 652, Box 54)
  - Governor Rockefeller, News Clippings&Press Releases (Folder 653, Box 54)
  - Greenway Council, Correspondence&Notes (Folder 654, Box 54)
  - Greenway Council, News Clippings&Press Releases (Folder 655, Box 54)
  - Harpers Magazine, Clippings&Releases (Folder 656, Box 55)
  - Harpers Magazine, Correspondence (Folder 657, Box 55)
  - Harpers Magazine, Miscellaneous (Folder 658, Box 55)
  - Harpers Magazine, William Tucker (Folder 659, Box 55)
  - Harpers Magazine, Magazines (Folder 660, Box 55)
  - Highland Falls, EAC Preliminary Draft Chapter 4, June 1979 (Folder 661, Box 56)
  - Highland Falls, Alternative Wastewater Management Plans (Folder 662, Box 56)
  - Highland Falls, Environmental Impact Statement, Wastewater Facilities Planning (Folder 663, Box 56)
  - Highland Falls, Environmental Impact Statement, Wastewater Facilities Planning - Appendices (Folder 664, Box 56)
  - Highland Falls, Environmental Impact Statement, Wastewater Facilities Planning, Volume 1 (Folder 665, Box 56)
  - Highland Falls, Environmental Impact Statement, Wastewater Facilities Planning, Volume 2 (Folder 666, Box 56)
  - Highland Falls, Wastewater Facilities Plan, Correspondence (Folder 667, Box 56)
  - Highland Falls, Wastewater Facilities Plan, Printed Materials &Clippings (Folder 668, Box 56)
  - Historic Preservation, Perkins Property (Folder 669, Box 56)
  - Hudson River Greenway Council, Nelsonville (Folder 670, Box 56)
  - Hudson Valley Project, FPC Correspondence 1963-1964 (Folder 671, Box 56)
  - Hudson Valley Project, FPC Correspondence 1965-1957 (Folder 672, Box 56)
  - Hudson Valley Project, Breakneck Mountain (Folder 673, Box 56)
  - Hudson Valley Project, Application Mountain Club (Folder 674, Box 56)
  - Hudson Valley Project, American Nature Study Program (Folder 675, Box 56)
  - Hudson Valley Project, Alternative Power (Folder 676, Box 56)
  - Hudson Valley Project, Legal Correspondence (Folder 677, Box 56)
  - Hudson Valley Project, FPC News Clippings&Press Releases (Folder 678, Box 56)
  - Hyde Park LWRP (Folder 679, Box 57)
  - Hyde Park Waterfront Program, Correspondence 1983-1984 &Misc. (Folder 680, Box 57)
  - Hyde Park Waterfront Program, Maps&Clippings (Folder 681, Box 57)